{
    "id": "5c6bbccf617a4759acf39c5ccc4e3de3",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He …………………. at six o’clock.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is getting up",
                "gets up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "God ……………….. us all.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "loves",
                "is loving",
                "love"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My dad ………………… for Delhi tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leaves",
                "is leaving",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………… a book now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "read",
                "reads",
                "is reading"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………. just ……………….. a call from him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am, receiving",
                "have, received",
                "have, been receiving"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They ………………….. each other for five years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "are knowing",
                "have known"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… the Eiffel Tower.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "have seen",
                "had seen"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………… in Singapore since",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is working",
                "has been working",
                "had been working"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The train ………………… five hours late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "arrived",
                "is arrived",
                "has been arrived"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "When I was a student, I ……………….. hard to pay my tuition fee.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was working",
                "worked",
                "have worked"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}